

CONTACT

- **** +6281282498637
- haikalalghifari1922@gmail.com
- Curug sub-district, Tangerang district, Banten

EDUCATION

2020-2024

UNIVERSITAS ISLAM SYEKH YUSUF

Informatics Engineering

2017-2020

SMK AL - HIKMAH CURUG

Computer Network Engineering

EXPERTISE

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Codeigniter
- Laravel
- Tailwindcss
- React JS

LANGUAGE

Indonesia

English

Muhammad Haikal Alghifari

Fullstack Developer

ABOUT ME

I am Haikal, a fresh graduate of SI Informatics Engineering with work experience as a Fullstack Developer at PT. Ganda Jaya Abadi and freelance web developer for 3 years. Have a responsible attitude, hard worker, good communication, problem solving, critical thinking, and able to adapt to new things or environments. Have a great desire to continue learning, developing and becoming professional.

EXPERIENCE

October 2024 - Now

PT. GANDA JAYA ABADI

Fullstack Developer

Develop and maintain company systems operating in the fields of sales, inventory, taxes and production.

September 2024 - Now
Digital Scoring Pencak Silat, Tangerang District

Frontend Developer

Building an application for the sport of pencak silat which includes registration, admin, statistics and assessment features for pencak silat matches.

Mei 2022 - Now Freelance Programming

Fullstack Developer

Create and develop website applications according to client requests.

ORGANIZATION

IPSI Curug sub-district

June 2024 - Now Secretary

HIMAUNTIKA

November 2020 - July 2022 Education Division

Biro Prestasi PSHT Curug

January 2021 - Now Secretary

IRKA

January 2020 - January 2022 Leader